our neighbor it has literally become our
belief system that that is indeed Human
Nature
and I want to challenge that today in
this Mastermind about sharing
when we observe
children when we observe babies
playing with other babies
they will share their food they will
feed each other because that is what
they have
learned from their parents hopefully
right
we're being fed by our mother and we
want to feed the child
playing with us and then comes the
era of recognition that I am me and then
the word becomes you know mine mine and
that whole era I feel is where Humanity
has been over these six thousand years
um the era of mine
um but to put that into a more
intellectual context the era can be of
course defined as patriarchy and the era
of ownership and defining ourselves as
humans by what we own and whom we own
and I'm saying whom because as we all
know
everybody under the king
was
owned by the king in so many ways if the
king said go to war you went to war if
the king said give me your Harvest you
gave your Harvest
Etc of course not always necessarily
voluntarily but as a notion
that's been
the case
and often willingly so because there was
this
adoration
of those that are the leaders and
we still have that today in the form of
admiration in the form of celebrity
cultism in the form of
admiring the Rich and Famous and feeling
that
we are lesser if only we could kiss the
the the ground on which they walk or
shake their hand God forbid
um as though
we need that
symbol of
something that we are not
and yet over the last 200 years there
has been
a new era of
realization that each human being has
value and I'm now talking just about the
Western world
whereas when living in cultures that are
have
remained in more indigenous
so social orders
such as some Native Americans such as
African communities that I encountered
in Africa such as
uh yeah communities where we
don't have
the empirical structures in place so we
come from this whole era and we've lost
that communal connectivity and therefore
we're okay with are not even aware of
the fact that
the West has only been able to exploit
to to be so
wealthy if you will as a whole or as you
know everybody has a car and we have
roads and we have phones and we have
um
ridges and trains and so forth and so
forth
because
we actually
in almost like a zero-sum game
impoverished those places on the planet
mostly the so-called southern hemisphere
where people
have been
subjected to colonialism and after
colonialism neocolonialism that is
direct exploitation of all the resources
without
sharing the benefit
and therefore we could have all these
cheap Plastics we could have all these
cheap clothes we could have all these
cheap cars etc etc etc
in the so-called developed world so what
we don't realize very often is that we
only have this kind of developed world
because we have impoverished and
developed underdeveloped
intentionally underdeveloped the
majority of the people on the planet
and now we are at a time where that is
shifting
where that Awakening is happening and I
liken that Awakening to The Awakening of
the women in society we're coming into
an age
where we have said
I don't want to be owned by my husband
anymore I don't want to have my children
sold to another family or to into a
labor camp I don't want to anymore be in
that position and while we will have
lots of women in today's conservative
camps who said yeah but it was better
for us it was healthier that we are at
home with our children
and still it cannot be negated it cannot
be denied that we the women are moving
into a new era of our own empowerment
and of our voice being heard in society
and still we want to have children and
still we love to be mothers and still we
want to be the caregivers and caretakers
of our families that is still true and
it is all possible so we share ourselves
into the society in a very new way and
that is not true
for all the countries that have been so
terribly exploited
and
just like
with us
women there will be some who say yeah
but it was better when you know we had
the white guys organizing our our life
and we all knew our place there will be
those
but there are less sir and lesser in
numbers
and therefore we have
bricks the the getting together of
Nations who say we don't want war
anymore
they are now 11 and their former
complete enemies like Saudi Arabia and
Iran are both in there
and they say we don't want more anymore
we want to collaborate and see if we can
call
support each other co-develop
collaborate in what we can give and take
from and to each other and for Americans
that is very very difficult to
understand
that there's such a notion you know we
tend to just suspect that oh they're
only doing that because they want to
rule the world right they're only doing
that because they want to
Etc because
humans have
the
the typical
the typical notion that we have the
perspective that is the correct
perspective and we project that onto the
rest of humanity unto our neighbors our
children
Etc
of course we know that we should be
putting ourselves into the other
person's shoes in air quotes right
and still it's so hard to do that
but that's what is shifting
that other nations as a whole are really
saying we are not about
conquering we are not about exploitation
we are about collaboration
and I deeply believe that this new form
of co-existing and co-supporting each
other
will lead into the next era of humanity
of course you know for those of you who
are into the stars and the planetary
eras I know very little about that and
I'm putting that out here but there is
the planetary era moving into the
Aquarius era right it's been going on
for a few decades already and it's going
to take another few more decades until
you really feel that we are in this new
era I always say I'm feeling it every
day
just yesterday
I was saying to a gentleman
who was saying yeah but it's human
nature that we have patriarchy and you
know and
this and that and the other
um
I was saying I wouldn't be standing here
talking to you
at an intellectual level
um that you couldn't even recognize were
we still in that era
so
I wanted to start with this large
picture that is actually providing the
background to
what is now happening in the world what
is now happening is that we are indeed
given the opportunity to begin to
collaborate
and that doesn't mean that the powers
that be the powers at the global Empire
which is now attempted to be that Global
Empire right I mean we all know about
the various entities
what we don't know is that behind those
entities those three letter entities
that are trying to do the finances of
the world and the rules of the world and
the health of the world that behind
those entities
are the same Powers still
coming from the Royal and billionaire
and owners of everything
and that
I don't want to use those words that
everybody uses but that group of people
still is behind
the new ways of luring us into
compliance and into
yes please save me from this enemy or
from this disease or from this whatever
yeah
so therefore coming into our own and
saying oh
what's behind the behind the scenes
is it maybe the last grasp
to hold on to those empirical structures
and maybe it's not the last it could be
other lasts
but it is also very visibly failing that
grasp
because we are here and we're seeing
those collaborative efforts
and it had a really interesting little
conversation with a client of mine who
was a bit upset that I was
being somewhat
she said what was the word she used she
said not using derogatory attitude but
using a
patronizing attitude whereas of course
I'm at the woman the patron he of course
comes from the word man father right so
I was patronizing in this conversation
where I made somebody realize that they
were still stuck in patriarchy in their
thinking
so
the awareness of these difficult little
steps that we're making every day
in realizing that yes there will be more
grasps of control and more grasps of
finding different Avenues whether via
via weather control or I've known for
decades that that has been a plan or via
bio weapons and that those have been
going on since the early 1900s
so all of those modalities
are however no longer really working
because there are so many billions now
so of course I'm
saying billions and they're not so many
billions on the planet but about two to
three billion of us humans are beginning
to understand that that's what's going
on and we're saying we don't really want
that anymore
we actually enjoy
collaboration teamwork
group celebrations
[Music]
supporting each other because ultimately
and that's all under sharing that's what
makes us
joyful and happy
and
fulfilled is the word
it actually fulfills us that we have a
sense of contributing to the community
so what does that all have to do with
health and
all those other businesses that I
typically talk about right what does
that have to do with what we eat what
does that have to do with how we clothe
ourselves what does that have to do with
the immediate situation in our local
environment
everything
because beginning with what we eat
of course there is the movement you know
more local more organic more direct from
the ground more foraging more backyard
growing more indoor sprouting all of
those elements
mean that we can actually physically
share those goods with each other
because they are not
taken or stolen from other places
when we get those wagon loads of bananas
from any Banana Republic that's where
that terms comes from right the Banana
Republic is a country that has been
completely submitted to a corporation
that now exploits those bananas and the
local people who lived on that land
where we now grow bananas
no longer has access to that land no
longer has access even to those bananas
and no longer has a means to
feed themselves
why do you think we have so many
immigrants
why do you think we have so many people
who try to find a better life for their
children because their land physically
and their ability to make a living has
been taken away
so when their countries are now saying
we have all these coups in in Africa
rebelling against the French colonizers
who were probably with the most drastic
and just
continuing in fact giving those
countries a document upon
signing their independence they had to
also sign
the continuation of colonialism
and this is all in French and I know
it's often not translated and I speak
French so I can actually hear the
original discussions and read the
original documents that is how bad
neocolonialism is and when these new
young people now say no more
This Is Our Land we want our land this
is our gold our diamonds our silver our
nickel our uranium you name it it's ours
of course
I go as far as saying
isn't it time to realize that certain
minerals should not even be used like
uranium
isn't it time to realize that
we made gold this value thing
that it really doesn't have to be
it's a mineral it does some beautiful
things and some good
but
we have assigned something to it that it
doesn't have to be
because then we can own it
and
we can hoard it
so
there's so much more to learn in terms
of coming into this new era of sharing
but I would love to hear a couple of
your opinions and or questions that you
may have and you can put the questions
either in the chat or
show show your faces surely you have to
show your face if you want to
um
pose a question I would love to have
other questions how does it impact our
life today
and or excuse me
I can hear you Ben
no I cannot hear you Ben for some reason
you unmuted yourself
would you I'll ask you last question
again please
are you what are your questions that
come up with this view of why we need to
learn to share
to you I have no questions I agree one
thousand percent okay
thank you
a group which I belong to you know the
the Oracle girl uh dot org group
we are there's a Planned meeting
in Vermont
in a couple of weeks which is about
sharing
hearing or sharing caring also sharing
yeah
because we know we know I mean I
I have felt for a long time the reason
we are here or or the
the way of being in our lives on Earth
is to be here for each other
which of course includes sharing
and when we are all here for each other
and not in any other way
everybody has enough everybody has you
know a place to live enough to eat and
all of this is possible
yeah beautifully said all of it is
possible it's just that 200 years ago or
a hundred years ago even 50 years ago
this was still a very difficult
proposition to make because people would
say well it's human nature to want to
have more than your neighbor to want to
be better faster bigger stronger
and that is beginning to change
I've often said and I'm repeating it
here again that my dear friend Patrick
babumion one of the strong man you know
was Rec world records in the world
who you know is strong on plant on a
plant-based diet
says it is no longer about competing
with others it's about competing with
yesterday
so this here being better than yesterday
um sharing of course also has another
aspect
so many of the people who do not want to
comply who do not want Total Control Etc
are talking about freedom
and I will say what is freedom well that
I can do what I want when I want where I
want
well what about the people who were
there before you
where and when you want to do what you
want
and then we get to
the actual definition for humans of
freedom freedom is not if I can just
kill and maim anybody
Melissa welcome
you found the working link
um so
what is it then that is freedom
freedom is the co-responsibility for the
other person's freedom
so then you have
again sharing right imagine a limited
space
and one person and there's 10 people in
that limited space and one person comes
in there and says I'm free
I claim this space
what about if everybody wants to claim
the space then we get to sharing the
space
so my freedom ends where I infringe upon
another person's freedom
and of course I have the whole
transaction has to be preceded with us
giving every human being an equal
right to be to life right
what happened that so few people talk
about is of course in the Americas and
that goes north and south
the Europeans barged in there and said
this is mine now my freedom
I can shoot maim burn down
and starve everybody who's been here
before because I have the god-given
right to be free on this land
so
it wasn't about freedom of everybody it
was only about freedom of those who had
the will to kill
my most opened email in a long time was
killing makes a killing
where we discuss exactly that
killing makes a killing and we're still
in that mindset even though we don't
realize it that we can just take because
there's this divine right that we claim
to
sub
to submit subdue
and
exploit others
just because well apparently they're not
as willing
to make a killing
as we are
so
um
but let's explore a little bit more of
what that has to do with the food we eat
again you know we talked about the
Banana Republic and
it also translates into of course what
makes the most
money
are the products that are the most
controllable and the most
um ownable is not a word but let's just
make that a word that you can own
and while you can own land you still
have to
allow nature to do its thing
and we've we've transformed the natural
growth of plants
and animals into our industrial approach
to things therefore we have
factory farms
we have Factory growing grounds now as
well in vertical
um growing rounds we have machinery and
fertilizers that and genetic
modification that are trying to
exploit
get more out of what nature provides
right and at the same time we're
beginning to realize how getting more
making more so that we can sell more and
make more profit
actually destroys the very nature out of
which we want to
derive our supplies so it will last for
a short time but then it will collapse
because the soils are collapsing
the
food supplies for the animals will
collapse because you can only put so
much poison onto a soil
and then it won't grow anymore and for
me the most ironic one is you know to
own the seeds that you genetically
modified so that they don't produce
viable seeds
so how much of an organic seed Vault do
you have to have in order to even
continue to modify these seeds so that
they don't grow but they have to still
grow they just don't produce viable
seeds it's I mean it's so ludicrous
it cannot
perpetuate itself because we have cut
the perpetuation itself off
in the root so to speak
so
if you understand that life is a life
cycle and it moves
in circular
motions albeit in a Direction
right it because it is evolution within
those life cycles
or adaptation for example when the
weather changes there's adaptation of
the life cycle
and trying to own those natural life
cycles is where the buck stops
when you interfere with chemicals Etc so
when you start try to own everything
interestingly
you're chopping your legs off
you can no longer walk forward because
the supply of that nature provides will
end so
I don't know whether I'm I didn't
Express that very well but did I make
myself clear
and I think so okay thank you Ben
um
so and a little bit more to
how has
ownership as a principal ownership of
land ownership of
um crops ownership of people of course
um and ownership of intellectual
property influenced this whole
development towards
ownership and competition instead of
sharing and collaboration
so we have this
interesting development again that
the more you own the more you erode the
supply of what makes puts you in that
ownership
let's have a little stretch like the cat
in the background
um
so the more you erode the the basis of
what keeps you supplied with your
profits and your riches
the less you will or you the closer you
get to the collapse of the system
and while that can take hundreds of
years
I am hopeful that it will only take a
couple of decades because there's so
many of us working in this new direction
of sharing and collaboration
so what do we need to enable us to share
interestingly we need confidence isn't
that strange
why do we need confidence to be able to
share
Integrity being at home and ourselves
in order to share
we need to have a
securedness that we're not coming from
scarcity
then you and I have talked about this
before
right in order to be able to share
we have to have a confidence
in that there is enough for both of us
for all of us
and that confidence is derived out of a
very different notion than what we have
been taught in competitiveness and in
in this fear of sliding down the scale
of virtue and value and
ownership
so when we have that confidence whether
we have a lot or whether we have nothing
we can share with joy because there's no
fear of
scarcity or of
losing
of loss
of sliding down the scale in the social
agenda in the social
um structure
so
what um what I'm going toward is that
there are new social structures that
colleagues of mine and people I never
heard of
um have
invented and are working at and one of
them is
called the gradito model
.net
is in in many languages now
and I would love for you to all explore
that
and because I've almost talked for an
hour oh my goodness I need to invite you
all to work with me to find your place
where you want to participate where you
find your gift and your confidence to
work your gift into the whole into the
collaboration with others
without your being at home in yourself
it is very difficult
because then we either
try to join the exploiters or we try to
join the victims which are also the
field we feel exploited we feel
victimized we feel weak so growing into
your confidence what did you come
to Earth
to do
what did you come here to contribute
most of us actually deep inside know
that
so I'm just letting somebody else and
Grace
most of us know what that is
welcome Grace
and as I'm going to summarize all that
I've said
I want to invite you all to ask
yourselves what is it
in this lifetime that is my very special
very unique very wonderful contribution
to the whole
and it's different for every single one
of us
it's different many people have sort of
invented categories you know there are
the supporters and the controllers and
the
um
promoters and you know they've sort of
created this character
um categories and they are helpful
sometimes for us to self-analyze you
know where am I happiest
I was just listening to
a woman who
had for 10 years had looked after
dying people in a hospice
and she made a category of five she made
this list of five things that people
most regretted
and number one was I wish I had been
more of myself
I wish I had done more of what I really
am here
to do of myself I thought that was
really revealing that was number one
more than I wish I had gone and hiked
the Himalayas or I wish you know all of
those things
but I wish I had been more of myself
and not allowed others to Define me
so
yeah allow yourselves and we all
ow ourselves to be helped by others
to step into that place where we say
yeah this is really really
who I am this is what I
give to the world and to humanity
so
ask yourselves that oops and I wanted to
put credido into the chat
what if we were all tied in the system
one way or the other not completely free
so how will the sharing be possible on
the large scale yeah you're absolutely
right Melissa what is it how do we make
this sharing more possible of course
there's so many approaches there's the
approach that we start in a small group
around us in larger groups but there's
also the approach that we spread
the concepts more in societies that we
look at what other societies are trying
to do among
among their population
um
it's it's yeah there's so many different
ways in which we can promote this
concept of sharing and of course it
doesn't mean that we can give everything
away we have because we can only live if
we
acquire monetary support there's no way
we can
live on planet Earth I always say you
know you have to pay to be alive
if you stop paying you're going to be
on the street and possibly
dead sooner
um
well yeah you
most of us don't want to be an outcast
most of us want to feel
a sense of belonging most of us want to
feel that we belong to a group and that
we understand and understanding is
another thing that's why you know my
latest email this morning was about the
tears I cried
when
um I was listening to Dr David Martin
explained so beautifully what Humanity
has lost because of this ownership of
everything and everybody
and the documentary is called
future dreaming
I don't know where it is available other
than on
I think I saw it on one of his websites
um
yeah we have lost so much by allowing
ourselves to go through the system now I
as a philosopher also argue that all of
humanity needed to go through this
terribly divisive and warring and
um
destructive era
in order to come into the realization
that we are individually co-responsible
which I believe is a new thing because
you can only really share if you are
individually responsible otherwise it's
not sharing in the truest sense it's
just doing what everybody does right or
being told to do things
um to cut the the cake in so many pieces
so that everybody gets one if I'm
sharing truly from my own
my own
I'm sharing truly from me I have to have
that's why I said you have to have
confidence but I also have to have a
sense of I'm individually responsible
for my actions
I'm not the victim I'm not forced I'm
not the
performer of that which is asked of me
but I am making the decision that I am
the one sharing so in order to come into
an individual corresponsibility
we may have had to go through these
thousands of years of
dividing us into different groups at War
Etc
because I think at least everything that
I can find the eras before
had more of a group consciousness
among others Rhian Eisler describes that
in the chalice and the blade
and when you look at very old cultures
from
a hundred thousand years ago
and older and yes they were there I am I
am aware and
um trust that they were I understand
that they were I don't like the word
believe
because it in and of itself suggests
that it's not true we just believe it
right
so um
so from an era in which we had more of a
clan Consciousness more of a family
group Consciousness in which we were
co-thinking about things we are now
coming into an individual Sinker era
and we have to create Community out of
our individual
decision to join or create that
community
and that's a very different notion it
makes us literally for the first time
responsible each and every one of us not
just the king who by the way also wasn't
really responsible because they would
say well I got the command from God
right or from
the next king
so this is the time where we become
co-responsible for our actions
and I'm saying Co because of course we
still are in the structure of society so
we can't just
scramble everything
and make a clear and decisive individual
decisions we're still in the grip of
that which is
but within that we can find others who
have the sense of this co-responsibility
and therefore and again talking to
Melissa
um
finding those
that are on the path
is part of the Journey of coming into
our
intentional communities you know not for
nothing are there so many thousands and
thousands of intentional communities
around the globe now
Eco Villages and hippie Villages and
religious Villages and all kinds of
different belief systems and
philosophies but people who get together
because they're not blood relatives
they're not of the same profession
they're not of the same background or a
monetary level of riches but they come
together because they individually
decide this is where I want to belong
oh this is where I want to collaborate
does that make sense so therefore also
sharing is the next era of us being
individually co-responsible
same with
freedom is being corresponsible for the
other person's freedom
yeah
um
and of course in order to live more of
that we need an entirely different
system you know people say yeah but look
what communism and socialism did they
made it worse
yeah because
yes and no I
trust or I understand that those
movements have made contributions to our
understanding of
that the old hierarchical structures are
not the only ones
viable anymore right the farmer can now
be the professor and the professor can
now be a mason or or that family you
know the the clan system has been broken
by those big
Socialist Communist movements ironically
however because we still have the super
super structure
when you really dig deep you learn that
those two were largely funded by the
world money holders
you know two of them start with the
letter R and you may very well know who
they are
our o actually about you know one in the
banking and money industry the other one
in the
um ownership of
railroads and then there's Carnegie and
others that belong to that and all the
royalties belong to that Clan
until not so recently they were called
the Builder Burgers that's now
transformed into another into a
three-letter acronym
and again I don't want to talk about
what they are now I think you can all
understand what they are
so
we
can see that
what has been attempted
as a liberation of
the
the labor force the the Surfs the ETC
the slave populations
has
however changed achieved the system in
spite of the fact that those movements
were co-sponsored
and corrupted back into a dictatorship
in many cases
yeah thank you for that Melissa I'm just
reading your
your your
um chat
text all right let us wrap up
and for all of you who are listening to
this later
please feel free to still ask your
questions in the comments
and I will see them
and I will respond
um my YouTube channel is not big yet
I've only just started a podcast
and you find me under johanna's raw
foods
on YouTube all my activities on YouTube
and my uploads are under that and the
whole Mastermind series is there and of
course Johannes rawfoods.com is the
website where you can connect with me
via the contact button but also wherever
you see this content feel free to
connect because again it starts with
connection and I love helping people
grow into their own very individual
power
that's part of my gift to the world
and yes I still have to pay my bills
it's not all for free but it's a lot
less than in most other situations
so
in short
and wrapping it up
the next era is about sharing we better
learn now because we also have to learn
as prices are rising because
the cheap Provisions are no longer as
cheap
and we have to learn to waste less
that's actually on my big list here that
I tend not to even look at once I get
started so
we have to
learn to waste Less in the West
we have to learn to use local Resources
with each other share with each other
and
be aware
of
that which we have
coming because of the exploitation of
others and reversely
be encouraging our children and
grandchildren
to love the fact that they're growing
into this era
of much Freer individual human beings
who are allowed to be just good humans
as opposed to
being part of these oppressive systems
it's a beautiful thing
and yes they're trying but they're not
going to get away with it
the grasping is over
all right
any last words any comments
from those present I would love to hear
whether in the in the chat or in
Grace says hi Johanna nice to see you
and catch up I miss the time just want
to say hello thank you Grace great to
hear from you I hope you're doing well
and
you know feel free to
um book a time with me you know the
those short Discovery calls are free so
you can you can certainly do that
um you can book a time with me
by connecting on my website or by going
to
calendly.com
Johanna minus three
so
many ways to connect with me
you've been very busy good to hear
this is Ben can you hear me
I can hear you yes I just would like to
mention yes communism didn't work
because they were actually
totalitarianism in in the world history
and we do have a history of true
communism which was the monastic process
where everybody really
uh you know live together and work
together and it was you know uh
definitely a unit and then also the
kibutsim the original keyboard team in
the desert
they were really uh seem to be more of a
sharing and really what you know
communism was about
right and unfortunately I have to of
course put that again into context
because
the kibutes were still
on land that had been taken away from
the people who lived there yeah
the concepts were great so instead of
going in and saying let's do this
together with what's here
that wasn't possible because the mindset
was not everybody is a human only we are
the important humans now right
so that's
that's the sad part about that but yes I
mean the the thoughts have been in
humanity for a while the thoughts it
must be possible to collaborate now we
have to figure out ways to implement
Implement implement but it's good to see
these attempts in many places what was
the first example you mentioned
uh monastic uh existence so you're
talking about
the monasteries monasteries and of
course they are either all male or all
female
and therefore again very exclusive and
you have to subscribe to a certain
lifestyle which then gets broken because
it's very very unnatural to prohibit
humans from any kind of love or
procreation or exchange of sexuality
so you basically invite
I always said you invite perversion when
you force puritanism
of any kind so
yeah but nevertheless we can learn from
these models because we see what they
were missing
right
and we can then do the next level and
attempt to incorporate the recognition
of Nature and the way that
existence on the planet works it works
oh in in my um in my podcast I was
talking about
that of course life
equals
reproduction
life is reproduction
without reproduction there is no life
because the life cycle has to always
grow the next and the next and the next
right and that goes for all of life from
the bacterium to
the human
to the oak tree
so yeah if we only recognize that
we we get we get ahead
and most plants are very generous in
their reproduction because they give us
so many more seeds than they need for
reproduction which we can then use and
no I guess I brought this up about the
two different uh two cases because
the rest of it was actually
totalitarianism and you know people talk
about communism today it's not communism
it's totalitarianism and the intention
of so-called communism today is still
really totalitarianism yes
and yeah and still
it's again a kick in a direction that
went wrong and we have to do another
kick in the direction to hopefully go
less wrong right that's that's the way
Evolution or or our evolvement into
a new existence on the planet hopefully
it works
these two examples were where people
shared
yeah yeah you're absolutely correct here
for each other you know which is yeah
and then of course you know hey it was
still part of what you call we're
mentioning now and then human nature
which
um comes most of the human nature really
originated thousands of years ago quote
unquote from the fear
of not
making it so then needing to acquire
well I again I disagree because that's
an era the era of fear comes with the
era of ownership possession and scarcity
right before that
I think we had an era of
this this Collective Consciousness which
you can still see in some indigenous
communities that have mostly died out
Ryan Isler describes it as the minoan
culture on the island of Crete in Greece
had that for a long time still so this
communal Consciousness where even your
brain worked in telepathic collaboration
with each other
was before all of that warring and fear
um environment
but I have met many people who live in
nature and have some of that indigenous
understanding of how nature Works they
don't have fear they don't have fear of
the tiger eating them or the jaguar or
the whatever or the snake
there is a communication and
collaboration
and yes you have to be aware
and yes you want to be doing the right
thing to respect their space so that
they respect your space and all of these
kind of things
but yeah
we need to learn from that
to carry into
the individually corresponsible era
all right guys
please communicate with me please allow
us to work together
please bring to the world that which you
have that is your very very special gift
and
yeah of course I mean reproduction it's
not just the fruits that are plenty you
know human sperm is also a plenty and
one man could literally repopulate if
that were the way it worked but it
doesn't it only works that some
have this purpose and others have
another purpose and others are just part
of the production
so yeah of course sperm also is a plenty
and very wasteful if you will you know
so are human eggs I mean I probably
still have a bunch of eggs in my womb
that I will never be able to use
because they were created there or they
come with the package
right yeah
yeah
of course that's exactly it what what
Melissa is saying here that
artificial man-made systems in
reproduction
will ultimately fail
because the powerful
natural reproduction is
the only one that works on this little
planet you know we have all kinds of
ideas we should put our ideas to
collaborating with nature as opposed to
against nature
we can do a lot of beautiful things
sharing again sharing with nature the
natural
the natural energies and powers and
resources that
plants rocks and Waters
give us
all right guys it is late and I'm going
to wrap it up thank you all for being
here
and
I hope to oh there's more
um well Melissa feel free to make a Time
for us to talk
and and I'm I'm happy to
provide that time
all right surely I haven't heard from
you normally I hear a couple of
sentences from you can you put something
in the chat
and Grace just left
and if I'm not here you're from Shirley
and from 646 I shall say goodbye I love
you guys and everybody who's listening
to this at a later time I can't wait to
hear from you and hear your opinions or
also what you found interesting in this
presentation
okay and go ahead and share it makes you
so happy
ciao
no